<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Aamchi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="cafeholiday_title">Cafe Holiday</string>
    <string name="cafe_desc">Cafe Holiday, designed by Minnie Bhatt, offers a Santorini-inspired atmosphere with hues of blue, white, and natural materials like wood, jute, and cotton rope. The cafe features a relaxed outdoor space with swings, an arched entrance, and a terracotta-black tile floor. Indoors, minimalistic decor complements a menu ranging from continental to Asian cuisine and desserts.</string>
    <string name="cafe_add"> 7/11, Meera Apts, Juhu Versova Link Rd, opp. Versova Social, Seven Bunglow, Andheri West, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400053</string>
    <string name="gulshan_title">Gulshan-e-Iran</string>
    <string name="gulshan_desc">Gulshan-E-Iran is a well-known restaurant specializing in Mughlai cuisine with a unique Iranian influence. Famous for its affordable yet flavorful dishes, the must-try is Dabba Ghost, a tender mutton dish in a rich gravy. It’s a popular spot for delicious, hearty meals, ideal for budget-conscious diners near Crawford Market.</string>
    <string name="gulshan_add">Address: 15, MRA Marg, Musafir Khana Road, Crawford Market, Mumbai CST Area.</string>
    <string name="usmaniya_title">Usmaniya Hotel</string>
    <string name="usmaniya_desc">Located near Mohammed Ali Road, this Mughlai gem serves flavorful dishes like paya and kheema ghotala. It’s a favorite among those seeking authentic, budget-friendly Mughlai food with rich gravies and tender meats. The modest setting makes it ideal for casual dining.</string>
    <string name="usmaniya_add">9 D, Madina Building, SS Musafirkhana Road, Mumbai CST Area..</string>
    <string name="metro_title">Cafe Metro</string>
    <string name="metro_desc">Situated near Metro Cinema, this cozy spot is perfect for enjoying delectable kebabs and falooda shakes. While the interiors are basic, the food quality shines, offering a relaxed dining experience in the busy Marine Lines area. The upstairs seating is a respite from Mumbai’s heat.</string>
    <string name="metro_add">5/A, Jehangir Mansion, 1st Marine Street, Marine Lines.</string>
    <string name="juhu_title">Juhu Beach</string>
    <string name="juhu_desc"> Juhu Beach is one of the most popular beaches in Mumbai, known for its vibrant atmosphere, delicious street food, and stunning sunsets. It\'s a great place to relax, people-watch, and enjoy the beachfront views.</string>
    <string name="juhu_add">Juhu, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400049, India</string>
    <string name="chow_title">Chowpatty Beach</string>
    <string name="chow_desc">Chowpatty Beach is another iconic beach in Mumbai, famous for its bustling atmosphere, delicious street food, and stunning views of the Arabian Sea. It\'s a popular spot for locals and tourists alike.</string>
    <string name="chow_add">Girgaon Chowpatty, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400007, India</string>
    <string name="aksa_title">Aksa Beach</string>
    <string name="aksa_desc">Aksa Beach is a quieter and more secluded beach compared to Juhu and Chowpatty. It offers a peaceful atmosphere and is ideal for those seeking a tranquil escape from the city\'s hustle and bustle.</string>
    <string name="aksa_add"> Aksa Beach Road, Malad West, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400064, India</string>
    <string name="vers_title">Versova Beach</string>
    <string name="vers_desc">Versova Beach is known for its beautiful sunsets and is a popular spot for water sports like surfing and windsurfing. It\'s also home to the annual Ganesh Chaturthi celebrations, where thousands of people gather to immerse the idols of Lord Ganesha into the sea.</string>
    <string name="vers_add">Versova Beach Road, Andheri West, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400061, India</string>
    <string name="colaba_title">Colaba Causeway</string>
    <string name="colaba_desc"> Colaba Causeway is a bustling shopping street known for its wide variety of shops selling everything from clothes and accessories to souvenirs and street food. It\'s a great place to haggle for bargains and experience the vibrant atmosphere of Mumbai's street markets.</string>
    <string name="colaba_add">Colaba Causeway, Colaba, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400001, India</string>
    <string name="linking_title">Linking Road</string>
    <string name="linking_desc"> Linking Road is a popular shopping destination in Mumbai, offering a wide range of clothing, accessories, and home decor items. It\'s known for its trendy boutiques, high-street brands, and vibrant street markets.</string>
    <string name="linking_add">Linking Road, Bandra West, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400050, India</string>
    <string name="crawford_title">Crawford Market</string>
    <string name="crawford_desc">Crawford Market is a historic market known for its diverse range of products, including fruits, vegetables, spices, textiles, and household items. It\'s a great place to experience the local culture and find unique items.</string>
    <string name="crawford_add">Crawford Market, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400001, India</string>
    <string name="phoenix_title">Phoenix Marketcity</string>
    <string name="phoenix_desc">Phoenix Marketcity is a modern shopping mall offering a wide range of international and Indian brands, including fashion, electronics, home decor, and entertainment options. It\'s a great place for a leisurely shopping experience with a variety of dining and entertainment options.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_add"> Phoenix Marketcity, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400052, India</string>
    <string name="marine_title">Marine Drive</string>
    <string name="marine_desc">Marine Drive, also known as the Queen\'s Necklace, is a popular promenade along the Arabian Sea. It offers stunning views of the cityscape and is a great place for evening walks, jogging, and cycling. It\'s a popular spot for couples and families to enjoy the sea breeze and relax.</string>
    <string name="marine_add">Marine Drive, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400001, India</string>
    <string name="asiatic_title">Asiatic Library</string>
    <string name="asiatic_desc">The Asiatic Library is a renowned research institution and library with a vast collection of books, manuscripts, and historical artifacts. It\'s a great place for history buffs and scholars to explore the rich cultural heritage of India and the world.</string>
    <string name="asiatic_add">Asiatic Society of Mumbai, Fort, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400001, India</string>
    <string name="flora_title">Flora fountain</string>
    <string name="flora_desc">Popular Book Store: Located near Flora Fountain, Popular Book Store is a well-known chain with a wide range of books, magazines, and stationery.</string>
    <string name="flora_add">Veer Nariman Road, Mahatma Gandhi Road, Kala Ghoda, Fort, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400001</string>
</resources>
